quietagent.com 2011-03-25

# Privacy Policy – QuietAgent

Last updated: November 10, 2010

QuietAgent, Inc. is committed to protecting the privacy of our Website users. This Privacy Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how QuietAgent, Inc. (”QuietAgent”, “we”, “us”, “our”) uses and safeguards information users provide while using QuietAgent.

**1 Personal Information We Collect:** We may collect limited personal information from our users, including their name and contact information such as their email address and phone number(s) (“Personal Information”), in order to make a user’s experience with our products and services more enjoyable.

**2 Access to Information:** We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement. We do not sell your personal information to third parties.

We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as matching you to jobs or offering customer service. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us.

We may also disclose your personal information:

  * as required by law such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process
  * when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request,
  * if QuietAgent, Inc. is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information,
  * to any other third party with your prior consent to do so.

**3 Information We Do Not Collect:** We will not knowingly collect nor make available a user’s:

  * Age
  * Gender
  * Family or marital status
  * Sexual orientation
  * Color, race, nationality or ethnic origin
  * Religious or ethical beliefs
  * Disability(ies)
  * Country of Birth
  * Social Security or other personal identification such as Federal Tax ID, etc.
  * Any other information about our users from other online or offline sources

**4 Updating Information:** Users may, at any time, log into their account and update their Personal Information, by visiting the “My Account” section of the Website.

**5 Usage Tracking:** We may also automatically track certain information based upon a user’s usage patterns on the Website in order to make their experience with products and services more enjoyable. This information may include what they click on, the preferences they set while on the Website, what pages they visit on the Website, and the URL that a user has just come from and the URL a user may go to next (whether this URL is on our Website or not), a user’s computer browser information, and their IP address.

**6 Cookies:** Our Website uses a feature on Internet browsers called a “cookie”. Cookies are small files that Internet browsers place on a computer’s hard drive. We use cookies for enhancing a user’s experience when they use the Website, for items such as remembering a user’s login name and general Website preferences.

**6.1 Third Party Cookies:** Our Website may use Third Party Cookies from time-to-time, to show our users related products and services offered by another company. These companies may collect, store and use information about our user’s visits to our and other websites, however, we will never provide such third-parties with our user’s name, phone number(s), address or other identifying information.

**7 Use of Personal Information:** You agree that QuietAgent may use your Personal Information to contact you and deliver information to you that, in some cases, is targeted to your interests (such as relevant job postings and services), or provides administrative notices or communications applicable to your use of the Website. By accepting this Privacy Policy, you expressly agree to receive this information. If you do not wish to receive these communications, we encourage you to opt out of any further receipt by following the opt-out provisions provided in each such communication, and / or via the “My Account” section of the Website.

**8 Data Transmission Security:** We comply with industry standards of data transmission security to help protect your information. Personally identifying and / or credit card information you enter or update on the Website is encrypted using industry standard 1024 bit SSL encryption technology before being sent over the Internet. For more information on this encryption service, you can visit [http://www.thawte.com](http://www.thawte.com/).

**9 Encrypted Data Storage:** You may have heard of attacks on databases in the past, where personal information was stolen from an online database. QuietAgent encrypts any personal identifying information using an industry standard “One-Way” data storage encryption. Data stored in our database, such as name, address, phone, email, password, etc, is unreadable to a human and must be decrypted using the secret keys built into our technology. For more information on database encryption, visit: <http://msdn.microsoft.com/en-us/library/cc278098.aspx>

**10 Safe Harbor:** QuietAgent has certified its adherence to the U.S. Department of Commerce’s Safe Harbor Principles in connection with the U.S. implementation of the European Union Data Protection Directive. For more information about the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles, please visit: <http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/>

**11 No Guarantee:** You should be aware that when using any website and the Internet in general, that there is always an element of risk that someone can and will access your information. We are absolutely committed to protecting your privacy, however we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your Personal Information or private communications will always remain private. As a user of our Website you understand and agree that you assume all responsibility and risk for your use of the Website, the Internet in general, and the information you post or access to, on or from this Website.

**12 Your Agreement:** You agree that by using the Website, that you are, by doing so, accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. Furthermore, you agree that QuietAgent may from time-to-time update this Privacy Policy by providing such revised terms to you or by publishing the revised Privacy Policy on the Website. Any such modifications will supersede all prior versions after the revised version has been posted on the Website or otherwise made available as described above, and your continued use of the Website after posting or availability constitutes your agreement to the revision.

**13 Dispute Resolution:** Any controversy or claim arising out of or relating to this contract, or the breach thereof, shall be determined by arbitration administered by the International Centre for Dispute Resolution in accordance with its International Arbitration Rules. <http://www.adr.org/sp.asp?id=22090>

**14 You May Contact Us About Our Privacy Policy:** QuietAgent, Inc. is a Delaware corporation operating in Illinois, USA. You may email us at Privacy@QuietAgent.com, call us on +1-847-714-0077, Fax us on +1-847-239-6855, or visit / write to us at: QuietAgent, Inc., Suite 1607, 666 Dundee Road, Northbrook, IL 60062, United States of America.
